Guide to the George Pierce Baker Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1900-1958; Accession 2007-M-037
  - Plays submitted to Baker
    - The American Idea, by S. N. Behrman (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Beyond the Circle, by William C. Jackson (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Call of the Mountain, by Edwin Carty Ranck (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Educated, by Marian F. Winnek, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Glory of Their Years, by John Redhead Froome (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Gull Killer, by Hope Bartnett (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Hearth-Fire, by Rita Creighton Smith (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Her Flesh and Blood, by Eleanor Holmes Hinkley (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Hitch Your Wagon to a Star, by Edwin Phillips Granberry (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - In for Himself, by Mark W. Reed, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Jennie, by Norman C. Lindau (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The Lamb, by Robert Leven, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Mama's Affair, by Rachel Barton Butler, 1919 January (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Middle Window, by Eugene Pillot (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Molly Make-Believe, by Eleanor Hallowell Abbott, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Nothing But Money, by Margaret Champney (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Oh, Promise Me, by Phillip Barry, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Pale of the Law [fragments] (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Plots and Playwrights, by Edward Massey (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Prudence in Particular, by Rachel Barton Butler, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Rebound, by Thomas P. Robinson (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Return of the Prodigal, by Lewis Beach, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Stranger, by Leonora Loveman (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Time Will Tell, by Rachel Lyman Field (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Faculty production programs, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Student production programs
    Arranged by the name of the student who directed or appeared in the play.
    - A-Q, 1924-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2-14)
    - S-W, 1927-1943 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Programs, Yale University productions, 1920s-1930s (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Critiques of Department of Drama productions by "an elderly woman," possibly Miss Anna Burns, 1926-circa 1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photographs
    - Drama students, 1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - "Pop," Drama School custodian, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Yale "47" Workshop, Circa 1930 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Also includes a print of the glass slide negative (MADID #43744).
      - Glass slide negative of playwriting class, Circa 1931 (Box 7)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Access to original glass slide negative is restricted due to fragility. Plese consult the digital image (MADID #43744) or the print made from the original in box 6.
    - Yale University Theater, Circa 1930s (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Playbill for Pueblo, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)